Okay, so we can actually laugh at California. Good. God. Yeah, it doesn't matter how much it rains
There's still never any water here. We are loaded into the next match
It is gonna be Polt versus solkey this match will be starting off on
Dust towers those of you who want your tearing versus Zerg fix you got it
You have in the top right position representing CM storm
He's playing from Taipei today. He's Captain America. He's Polt
He's facing off. I love studio
Announcements. Yeah, well, yeah, I just picture you as like the the comedian and empty bar. Yeah as they might do
It's a lot better with it with the crowd the bartenders over there's like
Hey, thanks Joe. You know what as long as you appreciate me Jeff. I'll always be happy doing this. I do and of course
He's facing off again. Solkey in the bottom left
Good TV Z. I haven't hope so
I imagine I think of all the matches today depending on how I don't really know how sos plays pdp
But unless he does like a super super cheesy style. I'm expecting this to be maybe like a
Long series not quite as long click this one. I think this is a series that should go on for a while
Polt is very hard to kill so and he also doesn't cheese
So I think it's unlikely that the game should be super short unless solkey just completely falls apart
Some early pressure, which I also don't expect so yeah, I agree with that assessment and
TV Z's kind of been one of the if I think it has been these staple matchup of Starcraft 2 in particular
It's had certainly it's up and downs, but
It's been marked by some of the coolest most epic battles
Um, and I'm always interested to like pull I don't give into the hype like every tournament one of the storylines with Paul is
Is he still good at Starcraft?
What are you still?
It's like yes constantly yes, but he is facing solkey who I feel like even though Polt is one of the most
Accomplished in awarded Starcraft 2 players and he's done it in Korea Europe and America
I still put a player like solkey in a different caliber as as him
I feel like solkey is a world-class top tier player who solely plays in Korea and does exceptionally well
Which I think is an incredibly different level of a feat
That being said I'm enjoying this little bit of reset
Where in legacy the void the game itself is different but also the patches have radically changed the game
Kind of back and forth we're still in that formative period of time where
Yes, we had a really long beta, but because a lot of players were still playing hard to swarm
It wasn't truly a we weren't seen the best
Excessible play and I I'm interested. I agree. I tend versus there. I get in a pretty interesting spot
I'm mostly concerned
I guess curious or interested whatever word anything fits best you are titillated. Yes. I am titillated at the prospect of a Palt Taren versus Zerg because I know
Based on what other Korean Terran's have been doing and what people have been talking to me about their strategies and legacy of the void is that
It is mostly centered around
Building a ton an endless stream of Marines enforcing them a down-year opponents throughout before they can get ultra-lisks out
Which he kind of has been since the end of the movie but
The ultra's is the new part it used to just be like parade push forever until Zerg. It's a critical mass
But I'm enjoying it a lot more
Yeah, the thing was I used to be that you would you would tech up or you know and the Zerg would sometimes never make it to high
If they had a good mid game. Yep, they'd get the hive
But then it kind of came down to like who could micro who could control who could macro better
But now it's like if you're Taren and they get to ultra's you have to do something else like there's no
There's no walking up to your opponent knocking down his sport
Bible shows pop and you're like I can micro through this with mass marine like no, it's not happening
Like you will lose everything so you have to keep in mind ghosts are a great option liberators are a phenomenal option as well
I'm interested when the matchup kind of more settles and the meta's kind of figured out
I feel like one of the things that kind of hamstring the matchup is it became
Very monobilled more so than I feel like any other. There was like the odd
All-in to his roach all-ins but other than that it was as exciting as Taren versus Zerg has been for the past few years like it
Basically was I mean wings of liberty you had okay you open up reactor halian delay the third mutus come out boom boom
Does it get brood lords they win if they don't you win and then in heart of this warm?
You know you you went to the marine widow mine push and I think that was a little bit more dynamic
You usually had more back and forth rather than just like trying to push and do in festers while they turtle up to
To brood lords, but in legacy of the void
There's a lot better options on late game for both sides
I feel I feel the liberator is a phenomenal new tool. It's been added for Taren versus there
Also early game. I think Zerg you're seeing different all-ins from them
You're seeing non-aggression because that that hive is so devastatingly powerful and it's a different unit composition
Yeah, Zerg has more options in the mid game when it comes to how they want to play it out
You know, we it's not uncommon of course. You know, please still doing thing push now trying to get a little bit pressure
But like ravagers I think we're such
They are such a missing link from the first two thirds of the life of Starcraft you so far
Wings Liberty and Heart of the Swarms are very much suffered from like I have roaches
Yeah, they're like oh crap. I still have roaches and no
Paul is doing one of those things. Paul does best as he drops this scan
He sees the spires close to completing he had these helians out for harass
But he snuck in that second barracks pretty early on and as this dim finishes up
He's actually gonna have a few more rings a few more marines than solkey should expect
So he's got an armory that's completing as well while he has his engineering base coming in and what Paul wants to do is try to
You know clear the creeps sure but also take advantage of the lack of possibly baneling speed
Which obvious which there isn't this early on in the game and try to get some serious damage
And he has stimuli as hellbats. Let's see what you can get done five banelings are on the way
Stim is now ready you could skin kill the creep
What he wants to push for he wants to get damaged in banelings are super late. He's gonna get on top of them right now
Looks like most of this not all yep
All our cancel out queens huddling in the corner five meters simply not gonna do it sixteen weeks about the join
What are you supposed to do? No bands? This is just pull throwing on another one of those those cute tines
This is this is what Paul does
He's a creative guy is I think most tarantlers the last few years
If you want to see something other than those standard builds that we've already discussed
Paul was your man for it. He was the he's going for that fast biking
Usually we get the fast second barracks and this actually interesting enough is very hard to the swarm of pull
We saw this all the time actually haven't really seen him doing this too much myself
Like you know if they stream that I've watched but I guess that's why he's at a time off. He can just pick up this force
Exactly like that. I mean might lose one med back there. He's actually gonna kill all the banelings
So he's gonna go okay, then I'm gonna drop the marines again have fun killing those what if that that play with the
The hellbats was fantastic getting all the banels like that and there are a few enough if he tries
I guess he's just gonna be content to trade out here
How's that his army looks cleaned up what he's shut down the third base
Pull has his own third base roach speeds about to finish but pulls got one one about to complete
He's got tearing vehicles the one on the way and one one for roaches is coming in while his roach horn is bleeding out in his
May in his third
But uh two-base sir not a fun place to be and there's just think about he's already got stamed combat shows
Very close like everything this game is actually just
Got super well in Pulse favor this easy build that he's just frozen
It's very interesting. I again kind of want to reference and this is of course a fact of life at Sarkhaff
The loaded rng oriented here we do see a lot of zergs
Opening up very differently from this they have kind of more of a roach ravager opening doing a two-base all in themselves
And I feel like in that situation of course
Pulse craftiness and micro could get him out of that
But I would say otherwise he's fairly disadvantaged like just naked marines against ravagers and roaches
Well, I don't know it's it's 50 50 but the point being
Against this build in particular as you said very hots
Yeah, and and really tough in hots like you had to have bannings at that time
If you didn't you better have 10 queens for some reason because otherwise you're dead and I feel like
Soul key is good enough of a player to perhaps make this interesting after this
But he is he's been gimp really bad and Pulse trying to push on in the map of two more meta
Actually quite a few more marines. There's only two bannings with this army
Of course the strongest part here for a soul key as Pulse has his one one is two two is starting up and soul keys on his way to getting is one one
If it's pretty close at this point, but a fight right now could you know kind of spiral out of it
I don't want to read too much into this Nate, but what what of the mech upgrade right there
I don't see anything composition wise that he's doing with that, but why would you do that?
I think Pulse just killed into the lake and I think he's just considering the possibility that he might build c-stanks later on if you can't
Stay out on the map and answer for all of this though. I mean is is there like a that's what I'm thinking
Is he thinking like if this goes late? I don't want to want to look back or something
It's really weird because I don't I don't know that Pulse likes the slower play which is kind of what liberators favor
Is he drops another scan of that main he's kind of trying to seize like well where are you going with this?
But really he just dealt he dealt such a blow to soul key early on that though
He doesn't have to worry like soul key can't afford to rush high where he would he wouldn't have had those roaches that we just saw
He would just die
So clear up a bit of kitten pulls back, but I feel liberators are just such a better tool. I actually
Think since he doesn't have any tanks. I'm gonna actually agree with yama that confused myself plus one
Ship weapons would have been really nice as
Because of the way liberator attacks where I think they fire in two volleys
They do a lot of splash damage every attack upgrade for a liberator. It is
Massive if they're gonna fight against air, but also shooting on the ground
You know every little bit of damage helps not that it really matters because liberators two shot every ground units or it has
We'll see where we go with this, but right now soul key is content with continuing upgrades on those road travelers
Just building raiders kind of a pair at a time which is also kind of keying in on the fact that he does feel like he's way behind
As Nate said not just going straight to hive and that's because
He feels like if he makes too big of a switch to anything he'll just die and and to be fair
Pulse selling that message. He's doing a great job of remaining outside the base and doing these drops and harass
Yeah, and I love this you're trying to pull him apart and you know
It's he's always been easier to max on roaches than anything else for zerg players
You know for a supply for larva
But this is still not a cost-effective army in the long run and pull is just pulling him in every which way
Going for these fights pulling back the air superiority is not there
No, or soul key he can't do anything about these drops and you know if there's one thing pulled loves to do
It's drop all day. There we go. Taren vehicle ship weapons. I really like to ship weapons upgrade
For the liberators he is starting to get a few more of them out and you use these to get board control the zone out your
Forces they are so strong very strong now applying pressure this fourth base again
A pretty sizeable force move at the middle of the map, but also so he said you know what I got to do something myself
Drop comes into the main it will be greeted here by probably enough since it is just Marines with me while the fourth base is going down
Yep, he does snipe that fourth base. Yeah, it takes a little mind shot onto some of those
Massing army he's gonna try to move in at the same time the brod roaches are gonna make the way over inside of the main base
Meanwhile the drop hits inside of the main too
So he's gonna try to deal with those roaches pulls back and now he's gonna make as an attack on this third base once again
He's got so many forces now there are roaches spread out all over his main base two two is not yet done for soul key
Oh, there's anything you can do to actually kill this army the roaches are going to town
They're trying to get some work done, but I just don't think it's gonna be enough that drop also lands back and behind the main base mineral line Jeff
Yeah, I mean the meta-backs have been allowed to live the air as you said superior to going in the favor of polt
Killing all the meta-backs and like this roach attack would be phenomenal
And they were for the fact that he's losing the roach war and both the evolution chambers and his third again and to be
Half the amount of bases kill 30 40 50 scd's for all I carry is making mules off of four or five cc's and he's got an army advantage
So a little bit too little too late soul key. I feel like did what he could this is not a bad plan as we saw again
If he was able to hold the fourth if the drops weren't happening
Then this roach attack would be what would bring soul key back into the game
But unfortunately just so much damage done to him again
Yeah, and Paul is just he's just been in a dominant position most of the game
I felt that early attack. He did you know to be maybe a little too critical kind of kind of gave him this game
Like it was polt's game to lose from that first point
You kill that much stuff you kill those mutas you kill those banelings you kill
I mean just the third base in general is a is a death blow to most zary players and
Soul keys he's never had a he never had a good answer to that because roaches were never going to be good versus the drops anyway
So polt just happily 60 supply ahead. I guess he's just gonna build up another army secure his main and natural from the roaches
Get a turd or two out front take this fourth base and then I mean this army right now could kill everything he has at home
Yes, it's actually just been sitting here, but he could the stem a move and kill everything he pretty much could
It's just ravaged back there and even they are gonna go to the front and this might look like a dumb choice
But honestly this is this is so key saying I'm dead. I'm just gonna try something really wonky
It's not even a base trade. It's just like maybe polt slips up in production. Maybe he's a little bit too confused on what's going on
We know these may be are not true, but it's he's gonna try this yep
He's moving in on top of that fourth base. We have the liberators here to help defend. There's widow mines
He could be tried to dive on top and this army it's gonna come back home
And that's that's like it's not the wrong choice because he actually can't make the wrong choice
But this is the one that I think so he was hoping for
And I love these widow mines. It's just like yeah, let's just lock you inside your face get killed
And yeah, I'm actually doing it. Where's Polt's army? Oh, it's coming back now
Great. Oh, it's all going to die. It's yeah, but finally
Here's the turning the frown upside down a little bit
So he needed much more predictive and better
Cross of vial shots and in that last fight he actually got him which is tragically the one that didn't matter at all
like he actually triggered or targeted himself knowing that he was gonna get stamed into any back to have him and it did
Demstained damage, but
That's the that's the cool thing about the ravager
It used to be if you didn't have mutants
Terrence would just drop you all day long while your queens are like sidearm lobbying stones at him
And they're like if I do this 47 more times it'll kill him out of that
We're getting there, but it's taken a bit of time, but now
And we've I've seen some super savvy zirks too that are like you're not gonna be right where you all right now
You're gonna go over that and then they they because you have to preampively shoot there
But it feels so good and that's that's part of the excitement. I have released the void to is there's much more
Expression of skill and we're gonna see more of this the more time that the players spend with it
Even in a position where you're behind like roaches were always gonna be like okay
You know my opponent makes a mistake
Maybe the roaches bring me back into this game
But with ravagers at the very least you have that possibility where maybe I don't have as much
But if I can get the perfect corrosive vials, you know, there is a chance
You know however small it is you got a better chance to just straight up roaches versus pole
But they're better in the in the hands of better players and that's something that I feel like
With legacy the void we have a lot more of that because it yeah, you're right
Like roaches could get in this weird situation where it's like I hit two two and even though I'm down a base
You skipped upgrades and you just have marines some kind of winning fights
And you made the wrong choice to not counter attack but instead come home and defend
But that's more like a move a move and choices which is still interesting to me
But we're kind of addicted to start up so everything's interesting
But in legacy the void it's like I have worse of a much worse army
But if I land these vials on those two metabacks I can turn the tide and it's not just a like right click on it and kill it
It's a I need to predict where you're gonna be and the other player has counter play as well like I don't know
Yeah, it adds a lot more skill into taking me actual engagements rather than you know
Okay, my roaches have low range move them closer so they can hit, you know
Yeah, the bit more to uh then we'll work with that was
It still exists but in a different way, but in sarcoph to the dumbest micro to me was like
Roach versus Roach battles where they're all just like shifting into each other
You know, there's so dumb there's there's a there's always you know
There's always you know as we're as we're loaded into the next game
There's always those people out there that I like they can't but that was beautiful to watch
I'm like no watching people try to dodge corrosive bile and land them is way there's a lot there's a lot more exciting
I find this game a lot more fun to cast just from that alone
We're loaded into prion terraces for game number two
As our zerg player who's down
1-0 in the bottom right is solky
It's a best of five oh no long way to go definitely
I'd say a bit of a more even match in the last one, but Paul showing a lot of strong play of course
He's the tanner player in the north and west and this map is the worst it's it's been what you're gonna say that it's
It's pretty topical content. Oh my god. You can't say it's the worst since your protocol is in the pool
This is worse. You really think so I do
I think any map where you could very easily take a gold
In fact you have to basically take a gold as your third and they're like okay, well all right, but on my fourth base
Oh, no, it's another gold. You just take another one and if you get to the weird spot where you take a fifth base
You got the option for that to go to two goals one map and that has led to this happening pretty much every game
It's done. I don't think there's any I don't think there's any good player that doesn't do a build like
this
The three racks Reaper sometimes if you know on any ladder five racks Reaper as well
You basically just use reapers try to kill the zirke because the economy
From that third and fourth base for zerglings and dones and you know all that infrastructure for zerg is mostly mineral
Based aside from the tech buildings and that's why I judge it a dumb map because look at what soul key's doing. Soul key knows that's what he's facing
Uh pretty much 100% you get pretty much assumed that most opponents will do this otherwise the goal base shouldn't do that in a fan
You shouldn't go into a map where both players in
Starcraft you
Just kind of know what their opponent's gonna do and this is what I do
Like if the medicates that if the matchup gets there okay, that's part of the game, but when the maps is
You must kill them before the full minute mark strikes 12 doffeth and then you're dead and it's that's not good
So this I mean the three racks Reaper when zergs have tried to go for the fast gold base
Sometimes it can kind of give you a much easier time because the gold is harder to reach for the lanes and the cleans
But by taking the normal natural expansion it will be a lot harder for pull to get damage them with this
He's made a large commitment with this Reaper push
Usually zerg players are just gonna try to get speed get a lot of links around the knock them down
But very clearly it makes that trickies. Yes, but keep making queens. It's not actually thelings that's gonna keep them alive
It's the queens the the lanes are just to buy enough time for there to be 300 queens
Yeah, because as you said with the grenades if you make infinity lings
You are gonna be a part of a reddit highlight reel where your 35lings go for a surround
They chuck grenades at their feet and then laugh as all of them die
Yep, and this map does have those features as we see the things are trying to push these reapers back
I mean a surround you would be deadly by that
Look at the maids not too many reapers do get caught. Yeah. Yeah, I mean it was good for the zerg there
But even that one Reaper builds are still very heavily
Based around momentum. This isn't halo though. I mean in what like battle situation? Are you like dropped arm?
Drop the grenades at your feet, but sir
That's still a drop time. You don't know these reapers have the martyrdom perk. Hey, do man
Always always gotta drop those grenades
He's already put in the bunker behind his wall expecting a counter, but there will be
And no such thing he doesn't he's not really minding anymore gas. It doesn't look like he's got he actually has enough gas
If you were to build an evil chamber like I've seen some zergs
I do like a counter drop as well, which is really frustrating because you always want to keep your reapers out on the map
Yeah, but of course this is where this is where it begins
He takes the more difficult to secure gold base early
He can start to spread creep from there
And then it becomes really hard to push into this base because all of your production just gets rally here
And good luck killing the base then so the reapers are gonna jump into the main base
Paul is looking for an opportunity
Zerglings are pretty fast though. Are there enough of them that counter is gonna go be denied
Because the grenades begin to fly in time
He's not he's still building reapers just reapers. Okay, the reapers are out so now that counter attack is denied
Oh, needs himself. It's really mad. They'll heal on a second here
But I feel like part of the reason the bunker everything showed up was also because he lost those initial two
Yeah, you know, it's lots of other sales. I'd say that puts you in panic mode to some extent losing any number of reapers early on
Just because they scale so ridiculously well. Oh, it's mad. Then you have this little spot here where it's like well
You would like to get these reapers, but no, not happening
You just dropping your nids are yeah, I feel like Polk could actually be a lot better about grenades more active about them
Um to put on my cast or monocle where I criticize for the best players
You know, it could be you know, he could just become a machine and just do it perfectly
I think that would be a really benefit
Honestly, let's ask ourselves why he hasn't already, you know, he does this for a living
Why haven't why aren't these guys? Why aren't these guys in like test medical studies for like cyber cybernetics
Arms and legs that they don't actually have like the wrist issues anymore from playing
Oh, that'll be a shing face. You know, they already took out like guys that have the prosthetic leg that actually helps them run faster
What if there's a time
When they start wondering in games, it's like guys that have games hooked up to their brain
If we got a band them all the reapers died here by the way
Yeah, I mean at some point that you had you kind of do this and this is actually a pretty normal phase
He's just like okay really yeah, I mean at some point this is the reaper at some point you got to look back at your base and start
Macroing man, I lost all the reapers whatever he's like is he's got double gold. I'm sure I'm fine
I think a couple of men have actually had fix
There's a reason why he made that investment to reapers and the fact that it hasn't paid off
Well, if he had just done nothing and let's all he take two gold bases without trying to defend
He'd be an equally unfun position. I tell the story once more, but but honestly
I am
Like if someone bms me I will be in you back, but one of the but otherwise I'm not a bm right I'd never I always gg
I don't I don't really say anything
Unless someone says something to me, but one of the like few times I've ever bm someone unsolicited
Was against cytoplasm a Swedish third player
On uh, gosh, what was that city scape gold base that the terns just floated to the metal?
A meditation station. No, the one that was on top of a building. I really should remember the name of this
Oh, it might have been before your time. It was on top of a building
Yeah, bro. It was one of the really common. I know metropolis was on top of the building. Yeah, people didn't float to gold
I'm a tropolis they did the things um, but he was there so it doesn't really fit here
But what he did do is take his natural at the gold and I remember taking my hands off the mouse and just I mean metal opolis
Metal opolis, but okay
There's a gold base on metropolis
But they have so many similar letters with anus. I can't keep track of this stuff. All right
Anyways, it's really only times I ever bm someone unsolicited
I was like I was like you're how do you sleep and I you dirty scumbag?
Well, so he's gonna be able to afford to build infinite roaches
His he does have two gold bases mining now as Polt has just landed his third
But of course this map is so open like Polt's gonna
It's a tough third you need so much to defend that so he's gonna push out. He's gonna try to do something here
But I don't think there's any meta-vacs. So this is this is really risky
Uh
Risky's a word for it. I guess he's got sim and combat shield. No, it's dead
This is dead without meta-vacs
What Polt's trying to like this is kind of getting close. He missed the corrosive
Ah, I want to get excited about this. I'm not gonna. I'm not gonna stop you let your let your passion flag fly
Get excited about this
Uh, well, you know, you know if I criticize Polt's push here, then it's just my bias showing so say it for your save it for me
Yeah, save it for your stream. There's yeah, I mean, I know what Polt's doing here because because they're both on the same page
So he's like all right got both gold saturated
I'm upgrading whatever. I'm just gonna from this point forward. It's four hatch production. You can't hold your stuff
So let me let me ask you this then why would Polt veto larylac crest instead of this map
I think Polt's asking that question right now as well
Is like I thought my reaper micro would be better. I thought I could just walk reapers at him and win. No, bro
No, and that taking these gold so early like the creep spread is really pushed far out now from the northeast
So try to escape. Yeah, he's still doesn't have g. There's still no meta-vacs out here like he's
I mean at some point so he's just oh that's right Polt doesn't gg. I forgot now. This will go on for a little while longer
Yeah, Polt doesn't die very quickly
But guys, ladies and gents at home
Unlike the little bow game. I'm not gonna get this one wrong. Okay. If Polt wins this I will eat Nathaniel's pants
I don't know you like taste of denim
Jeff
Okay, two tears on the way for Polt and sulky six transition bra
Plus two carapace hosting that dream hack desk is really helping you up to humor. Oh, yeah
You're super comfortable in awkward situations. This is a it's a brave new world. We've entered into Jeff
Should I make you more comfortable and just say rotting the club after ever since that that bring you more at home if
The looser cast. Yeah, sure why not so he's still keeps maxed out
Or at least he could if you really wanted to I think if he built a few more overlords
He has the resources just maxed on roaches, but he's choosing to go for ultra instead because Polt can't really attack him right now
He's gonna go for a job in the main base. Oh, he didn't go. He didn't send his army exactly where Polt's drops are headed. He has some links there
You get excited. I just have
I mean, I want to believe right you got to believe Polt is of any of any player is gonna come back from
You know, it up against the dude who's got two gold bases then it's got to be Polt right you see that club great up there
The orange one. Oh, that's the GG up. That is the GG upgrade
I'm this matchup. It's also the one that comes out of the ultra-less cavern
Yeah, well, I mean that's the like if you're really being stubborn
My favorite part is that when you're trying to do this pressure
You're trying to make something happen as a tarant player and then go though you need so much to make these you need
You need so much to make these pushes work and like Polt's trying his best to get work done
But the problem is everything that he's invested into upgrade wise tech wise
Infrastructure wise is completely useless as soon as this kite is plating upgrade is done
Like in a straight-up fight
He needs a completely different army to win once there's ultra-lisks on the map and the double gold base is like he's just
Honestly like soul keys can in a really good spot
But you know as Polt increased in supply. I'm not gonna completely count him out here yet. Yeah, I refuse doing what he can't I you know what
I don't mind but he does he does have to switch to something else
Unless he's gonna try to win this game in some super weird base trade
There's no way he's gonna beat an army that's got multiple ultras and kite miss plating if he gets that plus three
Carapace as well
Three three upgrades from so it's gonna be through drops. Yes, pick off the fifth base attempt. Soul keys gonna
Double expand to make up the difference I suppose here
And again one of the factors that taran does kind of go into this this matchup these days knowing is there's not a flock of mutants
There are
investors so a drop could be devastated have to be very careful about that
But otherwise creep me and fought back a little
Fifth base being picked off
So the doom of taran is being staved off Nathanius the supply as we said clawing closer and closer
Yep
Important things to know of course soul keys can start to build up a bang from here
But his kite miss plating is ready and since they're on even upgrades
That means these marines and marauders don't really do damage against the ultra-lisks anymore
So he's gonna step out on creep blood
And then he's got to lift up and get out of here
But if he gets fond of a little bit of that
So a lot of medivex okay only gets one since they that actually would be gg right there
But this army camp you can't fight for soldiers
He has to just drop everywhere all right build up a liberator count and
Just hope that he can take a fight by his liberators because otherwise
He's gonna get rolled off for game observing right now by his friends late at night for her
At least Paul's doing his thing where he's able to get all over the place as uh that's what I'm saying
He's dealing damage
This counter attack I like this you know soul keys just saying actually know what's grievous
I'm just gonna not just end up in your service
I told you this what I told you the only way Paul gets it has a chance in this game is if it goes to a really awkward base train
We're on our way to a really awkward base train it's almost like you do this for a living or something
Yeah
Hold chaps that
GG
It's okay
Thanks
The timing to know
Time has been beautiful
I called this a really weird but GG is called pulled this
Pull this had enough I mean yeah, I think I think it's best on this map that you just double down
Go five racks one day so he would have kept chasing the drops and been like stop stop
Polt could have done something there he was to picking off his pension
Well, that's the thing it's like what what is the one thing ultra is can't really do and that's catch met him
That's right so it's like okay well. I know that marine marauder doesn't deal damage to ultra's so just
Move across the map with those build links at home. We try to clean them up
And then eventually pull it's gonna die because at some point you're gonna come home too. That's part. It makes that map so difficult though
It's it's actually
Well, it's a it's a two-inch
Distance is very sure saying like the moment where he's like I've had enough running this harass and attacks
You're already at third you're at the fourth. Yeah, the creeps reds in the center of the map
Which is a stone throw away over from that gold gold third base sound and that just stone throw if you think about the scale of those marines
That is
Of an ultra. Yeah, that's four football fields, but if you were wearing it. How are you sure if you're wearing a marine power suit
And if prion terraces has lower gravity than earth does it though?
Well, we don't know what we can speculate someone in chat knows
It's been discussed one of the law. Is it in the law? That's the old that's the only thing that really matters
Keep asking me if I'm ready. We are always ready to go
Attemptes doesn't even shoot that for an a fan. Is a stone's toss
Yeah, I forget I mean a tempest yeah, but a tempest with the energizer from the campaign would be able to because it gives like extra range
Yes, a capital ship with an electrically charged super mango weapon can shoot that range
Yeah, a space marine with a robotic arm thrown you said a tempest can't I just applied parameters
Right, and I'm now using your parameters
Play over
All right, we're going to Olrina
Well, I mean, what's what are the rest of these maps central protocol is going to be the next one and then ruins what a weird map pool
I'm liking it. So he vetoed orbital shipyard by the way, so he's just he's just showing how evil he is because he knows
He knows that's like a probably Terrence favorite map versus or one of them. I'd say dust towers as well
But um, it's tied one a piece here ladies and gentlemen. It's intel extreme masters
Tie pay day one in the top left of Olrina. We have the red tarant player representing sea and storm heat is Polt
You beat me on this map Nathanius
You beat me in a dirty way. Oh, I beat you with one of the dirtiest cheeses there is you did
Yeah, I'll get you dirty tarant
I mean a lot of people on this map that I should never ever be in TVP because of uh because of the ghost pepper cheese
Is opponent in the bottom left
The blue zerg player he is soul key
The rustic sense on that map makes makes early pushes for tarant really strong
I think it's a cool map. I actually this is one of the maps
Where we've we've heard David came interviews and even in reply which he's does such a good job of replying to the community and kind of talking about their thought process
He wants sub standard maps and a lot of times that can make a map really bad
And stupid like the game before but on this in this case
I feel like this is a healthy mix of yeah weird stuff happens here
But it's it's cool and it's fun in a best of series. I think Olrina's a really entertaining map to plan like I mean
It's it's kind of weird to say because it's like okay, you know
I do like weird cheeses on this map, but you you can do weird cheeses on this map
You know like there's you have a lot of options for super aggressive play you have options for
I like how super weirdly totally play you've got this really tight choke point that's initially on it
But even as the game goes on you expand away from yourself. There's no options to the left of your base like that
You are going down the line and then if you want if you're you know if you're rough
You're well. You go for the gold base in the middle as well. Yeah, thankfully. I actually saw an amazing highlight
I think from one of the catavit sick qualifiers where a pro-loss player got nightest here
You have to be more prism to the island and then he recalled his whole entire army there and his mother's you court no more energy
He actually lost he completely lost the game because he couldn't teleport this morning
Because he moved everything there. It was great. Interesting. Yeah, but see that only on Olrina
I feel like there's a hashtag for that that we should all talk about hashtag only on only only things that you're in it is
Just say Olrina or just just Olrina things. I do I do agree though. I love this map. I do too
It's it's a very awkward map a lot of crazy stuff happens here, but you know what crazy beats the same thing every game
Which we had a little bit too much of hots did a better job
But we certainly wings of liberty there was stagnation and
Lays of the void right now some people will probably tell there's too much weirdness going on, but I think this is a
though
Hey tried
I got excited about that scv surviving. Oh
If I was playing this game right now, that'd be a highlight right there for the scv survived, okay
It was like zoom in and out and left and right and like yeah, you guys all EDM music going on exactly your face like exactly
We get rangely warping in now. We get like the hit markers and everything great
Actually, that's something that this if we're talking about weakness in the starcraft community
Uh, not to hate on any one of the sLR and in fact
So you haven't watched any highlight rules from there or something like that, but
Other games like nothing, but like there's these famous highlight reels of other games that are really really cool and exciting
Every time they try to do it in starcraft. It's like
semi interesting micro slowdown 10x and then like
zoomed in and out and like gray and black and like you shake the camera a little bit
You know, it's like actually
Not that great. So supposed to go for a tank drop in this game. Maybe uh, oh just once you sink really okay
So it's a defensive tank. I still feel like using the meta-back to move across the map like this map is great for tanks
Cuz you can set up here and then slowly push through
Um, especially just as the size of the map is so small like as spotted by the way by the really weird
Is that a Viking at the bottom of that
The fan flow can you get a pick notes a reaper? Okay
Interesting. I don't know if we got spotted
Uh, but these links I think we're thinking about a counter attack, but are now not going to be doing that
But you can see how Polt's adjusting in this map though. He's not really like a I I would say he
He generally likes to play the macro game
But he's setting himself up on two bases. He's got this Reaper running around
But he's just going to base this game. He's adding on extra birds. He's getting stem. We're gonna see a marine probably like a
I guess he also go from marine mines since he moved the factory off of the reactor and this layer starting out
Oh, it's a light
Okay, he's got the tank watching the front so
I'm always getting outside of the bunker. It's my favorite kind of marine
Grab this overlord. He does start the third command center, but he's set up very well for two base pressure with these barracks being done
So early start building meta-backs and start going for
Stim that's one of the pull-ups specials though. He's done this across like almost all the matchups like a surprising amount of units
That's kind of one of the
Pulse
Warflaw. I mean it's a new game sure, but it's still pull right still pull pull is wanted
Pulse always bend that guy though because he actually actually frustrates a lot of tarant layers because they'll be like
This thing is this build's really hard to deal with as this job gets caught
But if Pulse just be like actually have come up with some really weird build. It doesn't make any sense
But it's actually really good no matter what so it's called for orders. He's oh he's kind of always been good
No matter where that's true to meta-lize
And around about sort of way he's been timeless and it's cool. We're seeing him here in the round of eight
Major tournament. Awesome. And if he can somehow get past Solky
I think that'll put a stamp on a good run here as well
Yep, round him four. But he's got his work cut out for him. Solky pretty dominant. Although again
I feel like that maps a little bit of a gimmie
This map a little more evenly matched. I was I was curious both players opened up a little bit more kind of interesting
Pull took the double gas trailer early on and so he opened up gas first which is again
Something that like very it harkens back to hot but was like the defensive hot
So if you weren't all landing off of that it was much more defensive
Worked spanny into the big game here. Yep. Pulled to start floating out there. He commands to enter out
He's got a lot of Marines on the map now
No combat shield there you just finally starting up
So the Marines are vulnerable. Yes, but there's no bailing us. It's just gonna be Marines versus
Ling ravager
He's gonna take this fire boost away. This is an interesting part of the meta too
like
I wonder the evolution of this we've definitely been in situations before in hard hard to swarm in wingsliberty
Where tarry players knew they weren't facing mutus and had air supremacy
So they did a lot of this drop stuff just kept the zirg activated kept them busy
Thought back the creep, but I feel like it's gonna be much more prominent in the meta now and legacy avoid for tarry
I can reliably do this. I'm going to be out on the map
So I wonder it probably won't have the biggest impact. But you know what I mean? Yeah a little bit
I like that he's getting borrow again. We saw I mean just topics which I mean you don't know what I'm doing
It's funny. It's rich. They're all playing. I need a more analytical commentator like Todd here
You know what I mean? He's on someone who agree with you on everything. Well, I mean I didn't want to say it
I apologize for having an event I wouldn't cite Todd by the way. He kidn't me Todd wouldn't agree with
Who he always TLO would TLO would agree with you on the opposite true as well
Charlie Claus
Well, you know what Kevin would agree damage. I think nobody I need to consider that your opinion may be the one
That's a little too out there. That's what I'm saying. Well no one agrees with you
I need to taste osu to start cast and start crafting and that's what I need
There you go
Well probably exactly. I probably can GSL have been firing up rest of the barracks production is going up for Palt now as he gets ready to
Begin the parade push across the map. I mean Paltrowing to do that though like the narrow path is
Yeah, fairly obsolete at this point in time. You don't want to take a fight there
And now that we go towards mid map well, I did do a decent job of fighting back creep
But so he has done a pretty good job himself
Nice mind shot grab some links
Plus to attack a shell of course
I guess marauders and Poles hold on to his marauders
I mean they don't die instantly right to the corrosive vile cell
They're definitely a little bit more sturdy than just my Marines again
Yeah, it's something that look at so key he keeps doing this by way. He will not make
You know 10 ravagers in a row he makes them in pairs. It's kind of interesting
I guess he's the one don't all of his resources immediately. Yeah, yeah, it's smart. I like it. I appreciate it
Definitely not the norm I guess like yeah, it's pretty common at least in
Games and since you watch like streams and what the zergs do like just like okay
slam down that team and then suddenly they actually like for that brief 12 seconds they have no army
Yeah, and then they get attacked and like oh god
Well, I can't see my ravagers lose the game or I could let my ravagers continue to morph and still lose the game
It's really nice
Kind of a big moment here by the way both clean see get picked off as well as active creep tumors on that side
The creeps reds been shut down pretty reasonably well by pull me keeping it at the halfway mark for such a small map
This is vintage bolt by the way his army's never I think it's really important to know as he starts to fall back here
That he's scannion saw that there's no hive on the way which means it's pure road ravager from here on out for solky
Who's max he's got a lot but he's got liberators tanks and some of these widow mines
He's buying himself a lot of time to continue to max out by using those mines
Seeing him pick off the widow mines by the way
It makes you it makes you wonder if against a good surrogate
What mines are even close to being worth it at this point and because they're they're like
Buying time, but that's certainly not what you hope for with your your widow mines
At the very least it gives him like he said time to get more forces out
But the liberators are gonna get snimes by the corrosive vials solky continuing to push in this roach ravager army
Just seems to be a bit much, but now that the roaches have been chewed through the but ravagers do have less hit points than roaches
So if the ravagers get to the front of the army they die pretty fast you're gonna pull sd
He wants to go for a big counter attack after this and imagine but solky falling back at the same time drops
Gonna hit that fourth base in the bottom right
He's got roaches burrowed and moves into the mineral line of the third base and yeah, hold taking a beating here
Very true choice by solky
He did have roaches to support the ravagers, but he merely burrows them to make his way to the third and I think I it was
Dangerously close to giving up all the ravagers, but
Was able to calculate the distance well enough and separate himself didn't lose all the ravagers lost a decent chunk of them
But does buy himself more time pulled losing that while not losing the third of course
But having disrupted pretty significantly is very dangerous at the stage of the game doesn't have a fourth base
And he's starting to mine out his main base. That's the another cool thing is the pace of legacy the void
You really like all of a sudden that harass becomes very meaningful. You're you're down to one base all of a sudden
I definitely definitely agree there especially with so few bases that you can take on this map
Especially if you stretch yourself so thin
He's gonna push in through the liberators taking a lot of damage from those liberators actually as they lay waste to this force
But I think the roaches and the ravagers are just such high numbers that falling back
Isn't as much of an option for pull right now the S.V.s come off the line again
And solky just seems to have beaten battered and bruised him to the point of defeat Gigi is called and solky goes up to
2 to 1 a single map went away from having to face off against gun tomorrow another three oh
If it goes that way, but I do like the game plan for solky
I think it's very smart for this map the third base not nearly its exposed to some of the other maps
But predictably is like okay pulse pulse a marine marauder metavat kind of guy as long as I don't take significant damage
Get up the four bases. I can max out on two two roach ravager myself
And that's really difficult to hold off especially with good ravage control like widow mines
By your time liberators good, but the second they're in that siege mode
They're gonna do good damage, but they're also going to die you're gonna target them triple click or what it's three
It's three it's three miles kill three miles and then they're gone and they die pretty quick like the cool down on ravagers
Is not slow like it's just it's like oh you have a liberator that's gonna kill two roaches your dad right?
I said like ravagers like they just you know
Like they they wear their infinite ammo bandanas into battle
You could they could just continuously fire like pretty much nonstop. Yeah
Central protocol is gonna be the next map and for that reason alone up. I'm extremely worried
For Polts that reason alone
well
You have no other reason to be excited about this match
Well, I said I'm worried about this. I'm worried about pole. That's your only concern. I mean, I'm always excited to watch
Watch Starcraft. I basically
Listen, they flew me into Burbank because they were noticing we were having problems with the Nathanius's wild claims while he's broadcasting
And I'm here to rain you in breath. Okay, so is it this see this see the sleeper agent. That's what Carmichael asked me to do
Right, that's fair where a plaid shirt and remember Jack
So say you were the one that went off for pry on though pretty hard
This is another map where it's not about me. All right. Let's not yeah, let's not make it
This is another map. I would be surprised to see the Reaper play come back into this
I keep getting asked if I'm ready. All right. Ready. Let's go. We start the game up
I feel like I wanted to say something and then a three-off guard
Yeah, but you know what I got it. I still really feel like Paul could have done a lot more with that opening
Like I feel like he opened three racks expecting to get a two-base push
But then soul key just went right up to three bases drone hard and had like even without the goals
Like he just had a really nice economy and Paul really for three CC after three racks
Like he was just he was just behind all game economically
I think I think you get the nail in the head with that last comment particular. I think if you open up three Berks
You have to do damage you have to do something and killing two queens and several creep tumors is nice
That's not really the damage we're talking about that is like I need to
Get him to pull his drones. I need to pick off a hatch like that kind of damage or at least kill a bunch of stuff
But but soul key just pushed on took a fourth there's like a light marine drop over there the two roaches
Just kind of like get out of here and that was it
Yeah, he dismissed it pretty easily
And I think that's also just another thing about that map even with the short rush distance the choke points to
Taxi'm on a really small, but we're loaded into central protocol
Which you think is the worst map, right? This is personally my least favorite map
Okay, I think it's easier because you don't have to scout on prime terraces to rebar all in
But that's just me you have to you know sometimes if you get cross bonds on this map then rebar all ining is a bit hard
But then it's easy to reperchise if you get these spawns for example
Um, of course the red tear player on the top left
He is down one two needs when the next two games to keep his is it one two
Yes, that's how bad my brain is right now
Yes, always the game pull one thus towers game one be crushed him
He killed the third
The third
Listen, you know, in my defense. He had five soul bats tank 12 hours ago. I was in Florida coming back from Mexico
That's fair in my defense, but also that's part of my charm
Because I know always know exactly where I'm at. I'll just abridged it for all of you guys Jeff losses passion. It's okay
Jeff had to recharge his passion, bruh
Okay, so let's let's actually just gonna do a reaper expanded single reaper
He's gonna play this map sure straight up, but why is this such a bad map?
That's what I want you to because I mean I played the biggest issues
Anything and then vetoed it now come back the biggest issues that everybody has with this map come mostly down to just the layout of the third base
Right pull has two options for a third you can take the option that's super far away from his natural
Whereas army would be like this is a big ramp you can't block this off easily
Speedling play early on is a super popular for that reason alone
But then you've got back rocks as well
And then if you're a crazy suicidal tearing you can take the third base outside their natural which is
At you know what this map has played so little that I actually think that happens pretty often because people just don't even
If you aren't even even thinking about it as much and to be fair if you could take that as a third
You know might as well just pf it just stage your marine tank all in from there. I do have a quick update for you
Now remember game one
Congratulations, but I did that while listening to your analysis. I think it's spot on I also remember some of the games here
And it is frustrating the distance between
bases and how that gets kind of big as thing is like could could pull break the rocks and make his third base closer to his main base
Sure, but then you have to consider that it's not possible
You're not there's no wall. You're gonna build that's gonna keep that base safe
Yeah, and then if even if you have your army here and then they just decide okay
I'm just gonna go here and then get this giant space and you have to go a really far way
To actually be able to defend against that so I mean you get these spawns and let's just let's not even forget whoever gets knocked down behind
Like if either player falls behind at all fish rush distance is step-s-of-war
That's my meastones toss right there. Yeah, that is that is your still incredible throw
But it's still a tough roll much more realistic, but if we assume that you know
You're either in a power suit or you're you know a genetically evolved being like a zirgling or a queen than maybe that's it
That's worth considering as well
Even space frames by the way are genetically engineered that's true
And then it also in power armor yep
Um
So I feel like both players again kind of the map dictated to both them like I think so he says I gotta survive
There's no fast third build on this map unless you are I don't know absolutely crazy
Maybe or maybe you take an injubane which is funny because there's this is what made me a pretty bad professional player in particular
There's always that voice of like this is what I understand to be true
But then there's that also voices like but they know that so what if you do the weird thing?
This is not one of the rows off. Yeah, you can do the weird thing now
It's actually just it's just so wide open
Like consider that especially like if you're gonna do for like plays to try to get inside your opponent space
The main base is massive drop play becomes an issue later on like just aside from the fact that you're all
You're trying to cover the wide angle and be your third and you're in your natural
Do you think it's terrain favorites? The game goes on them?
Oh, but the way the map spreads itself out
I don't really have an opinion on that just because I haven't seen enough games because everybody videos this map
So I guess that's one of the interesting things about this format here for uh for intel extreme masters type A's that because we start with best of
Fives we have a higher chance of seeing this map as I'm I would put my money if this were a best of three
Polks or one of these guys would have been at it even if I think this map has some features that favor
Reserve because at the very least you can spread creep which will add your army bounce between those expansions a little bit faster
But at the same time
I think this map would have been vetoed if the players could have vetoed it
You know, I I think it comes down to it's like an online tournament people just agree like instead of doing videos
Like we just play on dust towers or go shipyard and prion terraces or something like that and whatever order you
Yeah, yeah, and in whatever order you want and then if this is eric then instead of prion you ask for like arena
But for reapers man, they still have the same
Lifespan and sarcoph like just since they're the beginning no one is saving reapers for the end
Like that upgrade that used to exist where it was like a later in the game they have more point no no
There I think I've seen gunner someone
Of course someone that's like you know literal god tier use reaper is in a fashion where like you get these link bane charging you
And you throw like three grenades in front of your army. Yeah, but that's you know super hard to do while simultaneously splitting standing and fighting all of your other courses
Qxc used to when he was up like 17 bases against the opponent would come out with a volley of reapers. That was really good
Yeah, that was always fun. He's like yeah reapers with the grenades, but in wings of liberties like reapers are so good at sniping buildings
Lake Aintagom like okay if you've already won the game maybe
Which is when they would show up
Is otherwise yeah, that's how far behind him
But it looks like the spires gonna be mostly fake so some mus are gonna come out
He's just gonna switch back into roaches cuz the rush the rush distance is non-existent with creeps spread to it's like a you just slip in slide this
Right in the pulse base look at these mutas. This is try hard sarcrap. This is my favorite
Three mutas if that trick four meters of that tricks anybody
Let me uh let me sell that person. Let me just sell him stuff because I'll take all their money
Well, Pulse starting to clear up the creep this is a beautifully timed attack by away. This is Pulse best chance
Yeah, their upgrades aren't ready for the roaches. He doesn't have speed. There's not a lot of ravagers on the map
Is this best opportunity got it now he's actually pushed though now he's distracted though
He's looking back at the deal with the mutas. I'm like yeah, just just keep moving forward
It is let him kill something
I can feel good about their mere existence, but now this push is stagnant
Yeah, yeah, with go get the third or something with an army this marine heavy like a corrosive bile can splash and kill like three or four Marines per shot
And he's letting these four mutas cut his production down. They're killing metavex
Or mutas aren't supposed to actually do this. I think soul key like it marches down drop the cross above
None of the metavex pick all the tanks up and he's just gonna kill him or any of them actually as it were
He's just like tanks be damned. Okay, he's gonna save the last one
Does get out of here a little where are the hero mutas and they're just chilling look they even coming back. I know
Oh my goodness. He's been like the best mutas ever this is the best just for mutas ever made it literally is outside of him
I did one base meter rushes and one one game somehow
Harder it's more goes Ross well. They're shutting down this drop like they're actually gonna live he pulls them back
The three Marines are like I'd stay out the four mutas the dream god. Oh good
This is good. Is that good jump in gets the queen he's gonna push for but the tank immediately gets picked off and oh whoa
What the walking down cross files?
Not really enough to use this super focused on this metavex
But he does have to pick off the news because he's metavex well. Wow don't exist
By by net of x and now the Marines can't run away pull is rally
I guess the best thing about this is that this is like getting the third though by the way
If you're a terrain player, this is a close off of job
I'm grossly disappointed with that me too. You know the one thing about this map that is really nice for Polto is it gives
Terran that feeling of having warping because you rally your forces and then they're right there at your opponent's base. So
The thing to keep in mind though is there is no third CC that I can see
Nope and not even the fourth gas. So this is kind of it all in this is the main drive up
It's not a three-base map right and soul key certainly playing it that way. Yeah, well
I mean Polto's playing this map about as best as he can. I'm curious how many games he actually plays on this map
Because this is final form you think I don't know
I'm just not sure well. I hope it's not because he has to play another game after this if he wins
True, I hope he has something else up his sleeve they push coming out here
Uh down and supply fights in the middle of the map here though and again the first of miles will affect this
Ergans keep that mine we saw that earlier. Yeah, when people talk about you know the roach supply efficiency
But the ravager count really brings that supply efficiency back for Zerg in this in this expansion of Starcraft
picking off the tanks the close of miles picking off the meta-vac with corrosive vials gets in on the ravagers
Though and this is kind of the soft underbillion Zerg army, but it just doesn't look like it's as much
Yeah, it's better actually like one bile away from losing three of the four
Which is devastating. I like that he's sprinkling in a few links too
Just like either either shot or two and look at this. He's trying the weakest roach into a ravager. It's all its help back
He's like you see getting he's taking a trip to value town now. Control is just maximizing his stuff man
Supply wise though getting a little bit closer, but again, Polk is fighting against the same time
He's gonna make this push in one more time and you know that the weakened tanks are the ones that are least exposed
But he does get those anyway with the close about arranged on that is also pretty nice
How far they can cast it
It kind of needed to kill liberators, but in fights like this it does really really help and we're seeing this played out the way we're talking about
Like so he just has survived. Yeah, so he just he has the third base
He has more money to work with like if his main mind's out
It's like whatever I can move to my third but Polk's like I'm lifting my main I have to go somewhere else
And it's actually a long trip
Yeah, because yeah, I don't think he broke down those rocks either and now so he's just gonna surround his army
Pitting him inside or outside of his natural forcing the lift up
And so he's just showing the dangerous thing here too is with Polk retreating all the way back to his base the map is small
But from here
So he knows where Polk is and he's got overlords on the left side of the map too
So he knows it's not being dropped and when a zerg's comfortable like that
It's really tough difficult to deal with them because he's one of the ways to punish a sword
Yeah, he gets a link on that too
Well, he's had that there actually he's just so he's on top of things third base under attack though
And this is this is something I felt like Polk need to do more of and he's gonna get inside the natural here
Should get the hat and all the drones. This is a good pickoff. You really needed this you want to eat drones killed in the last battle
So really start up room for you lift up. Whoa, there was enough room
He only barely made it out and now this third base by the way all of a sudden so he was feeling great right now
Polk is doing this is about Polk does much now. This is the Polk thing. He's he's actually making it
He's actually making a game out of this
I am getting excited when you should get excited in a fan. Yes
Yeah, this uh, but then all good luck defending your third because it's so far away
So I mean he should actually have that completely shut down. That's a big army. He actually
kind of
Yeah, that's what I was waiting for
That's well. No, you can't play that. I mean as long as he doesn't throw all of his cross-abounds at it once
If he can always threaten Polk with that to keep him away
And really Polk has no income outside of this base. He has some minerals banked up
But that's it. She has to make everything out of that and the tanks are isolated away from the rest of the army
A great concave for Polk, but as the sieves tanks die this army loses a lot of its muster
But Polk's he's got enough Marines. He might actually be able to do it
He's finally got that supply leaf for the first time in this game. Good cross-abound again
San you this is gonna cost you if you're gonna chase me that one. Oh, okay pretty big third base still not under tack
By the way, do you believe Polk has a meta back over there? If the thing isn't hard to this warm
If this were just roaches then Polk wins the game right now, right?
But the ravager really gives Solky that ability to shove him back with the corrosive vials and that third base
He lost 20 scv's of his own total work against 23 drones 24 scv's you've got mules too
But of course that means you can't clean up the creeps so Solky can still kind of dance around you if you attack him
The natural that was never taken again pulled up a little dribble of supply
He needs to this is kind of the dictating fight though here in the middle
Close the bow going down in the front lines are all up. Oh pulls back the last second. She does cost a little bit
It's quite a few of the Marines there at that initial throw
But I mean pushing here without their food for it is also really difficult because that bio you can just catch you so fast and chase you
But it seems like he's making something out of this and he's like, yep
I'm gonna go to that base you must bring everything over here to defend and you know, it's just unfortunate
You know with the low econ
He could have tried to slip something into the natural now
But I think he's content to just try to knock down as much of the economy as possible
He knows this is a low econ game. He knows what's at stake and Solky
This is still everything he has though. I think losing this
Hope might be able to take in here if you can clean up all these ravages
He's able to everything's in red health. It's just by the skin of his teeth
Good cross-boss gets a meta-vax as well
But I feel like a lot of the damage is tilted in favor of Polk who kind of maintains that 10-ish supply
Getting a little ways from his base and I feel like and this is not a complaint. I promise you but this is where
Mules are pretty cool like he keeps losing the harvesters, but he's able to
Kind of stopgap that supply that will not supply difference with harvesting difference
Yeah, there's definitely no doubt about it like the Mules are
100% what keeps Polk in a good spot in this game. He desperately needs them his army is you know
Largely Marines 20 Marines, but in low unit numbers when you have these small troops fighting each other
Marines are generally speaking to me more cost effective than anything else that you can use
You can clean up these lings this marine barely surviving to get the Queen
He does finally go down, but I mean queen still
Endanger
Yeah, Queens low kills the four lings were there too by the way
So now all of a sudden soul key needs to partition more units over there just to hold on to that base
Polk putting himself in a tight spot here between his two bases is these roaches trying to go into the
Roaches are gonna pull up here. Whoa Polk making the okay never mind. I was gonna say he just started to go across the map
But I think that was more of a mental click than anything else
He is gonna come back and of course for it off these roaches
Which do not have telling claws by the way and our off creeps
And they should all die the concussive shell makes it really easy from the pick these off too
So a lot of roaches go down what is so key out just two ravagers? They're gonna try to come up here
Broward your car roaches going into the game. They got sealed off
Let me deny your mining wait neither of us are mining. So I hope you like 200-ish gas
Well, I shall keep you there forever
But a full medevac by the way made it's way down to the third base and that was kind of I feel like the game-winning choice from holdy's gonna drop out
I didn't into it. You can't defend this. He's he's getting some more roaches out
The only thing that he's had in advantage in as far as like the upgrades goes that plus two attack that commands
And he dangerous low the thing is to dance he can defend it
But it's just over time he can't really like eight Marines in a medevac
That's not four lings and a queen to hold off
That's like a significant chunk of his overall army is everything right here for the most part and Polt loses nothing from this
And all of a sudden a freeze of space for him. Oh the medevac is gonna be careful
But look what's coming down the map. I think it's three or four medevacs and that is a load of units
And now all of a sudden Polt has the space. I think they believe that I see speed. This is where Polt's gonna take the game
I imagine like there's just everything here is trying to chase this one medevac and then the rest of it is over here for
Pulled medevacs of bio
I guess the best advantage of legacy of the void with a low amount of
Economy you get is just you know floating those commands and it makes it a lot easier in these low-econ situations for tearing to keep keep jugging along
You never get to make that third base
He might actually just trip when this fight
This is so he's entire army the drop is also at the natural, but that base was never retaken
He's paying a lot of respect to these these impressive vials, but he's still chewing through this because he's a fast-paced Gigi Polt
ties the series up to you to I remember each of these
I'm glad. Yeah, glad. I got excited about that one. Okay, you at the right time
Polt also Polt David Polt does remember my prediction. I said so he has to survive and he didn't so then he lost
That's I don't even want to honor that kind of intelligence you bring in this studio. I don't even want to honor that with a response
But ironically you did respond by saying right? Is that weird? We're getting into the lobby for the final game
Probably on a bit more of a standard map has to be the final game unless there's a tie ruins of saris unless there's a tie
Which you have had some crazy games and there's a lot of airspace on this map if you if we get into a tie scenario
I like this as I hope they're split map and I hope we see a great drawn out
I will honor what you just said
This is actually a great map for ties because Polt has already shown he doesn't want to fight the Ultralisks once he gets there
This is a big huge giant dangerous scary map
And that makes it very hard to kill your opponent early on if you're tearing
Especially if they get cross-spons so he will if this game doesn't end with some sort of weird push
Probably get to Ultralisks Polt will probably drop it over the place
You called it Jeff. This is uh, this is a phenomenal. Can I just say for that weird big trade?
I'm really excited for the future moment when we have a tie
Because the tarant has like 35 liberators and they kill everything's erred but they can't kill the buildings
So they're just like you know they're like what's the cannon called? What is their main gun called?
Ah, it's a Concorde cannon. So the Concorde cannon the guys like let's bring sweet justice to the buildings
Can't do it. Why
We don't shoot buildings you idiot like this gun was specifically designed to extinguish life
It is the isn't the only thing in the game like that. I mean there's air to air and ground to ground and air to ground
As far as like weapons if you can't use
Yeah, I think so
Because even the Reaper grenade now still does damage to buildings. Yes, just very yeah back
The only you only units or whatever that are like oh we can't attack buildings or whatever like well storm like spell cast stuff spells
But actual weapons is there anything else in the game that does not target a building
I don't think so
Um, and just other than like I said some things don't shoot air. Yeah, some things don't shoot air. Some things don't shoot ground
Right. Oh well interesting
It is a there's probably something that absolutely is the same and we're just not remembering is we're in the middle of the cast and
It's too much too much pressure. We're loaded in though. This is it. This is a cider of this best of five the winner will move on to play against
Beyond the bottom right representing Cooler Master Storm. We have Polt
Who did a pull those best brought that game back from a tally spot where he was low on economy and that that float over to the top base while keeping on enough pressure to take it
Hand out well. Yeah cool game percentual protocol to stay the least in the top left. We have soul key
That's just kind of funny about it though is like
Somewhere out there David Kim is sitting in his
Draconian castle on the top of the German mountain with his army of robot monsters and he's watching that game and he's going
Yes, that is precisely what I thought would happen an interesting cool game
Uh, whereas you know 10,000 nerds cried out at the same time when they saw it was that map and they're like no
This is a terrible map, but then a cool game happened and that's actually something that's been kind of calling the start
All the way back to Brewer Nathanaus
We had island maps which were never balanced. They were always terrible
But some of the coolest games you ever saw were on island maps
Yep, there aren't that many actually even in like the
The Blizzard made maps that you can look at what cool games
No, I mean
Is not really any island maps is only one and there's only one island map that you can you can just play that's Blizzard made and it is
So it is I'm pretty sure it's the smallest possible size excellent
That you can make a map like there's I don't think it's actually been attempted to make a good island map
Which is interesting something because they're very they're outspoken about wanting unique maps
Yeah, let's do it. Let's get island maps the only island map you can play right now
Actually just has like five bases and it's for four players designed like that. Oh, that's terrible. Yeah
It's pretty awesome sounds down right down. Yeah
There you go. Give us an island map. See it
Let's get some
Not right as standard. I want to see late game stuff. I'll see spells flying
This this game right here with cross spawns on ruins of Saras
It's this is like the longest rush distance I'm pretty sure of any of the maps right now biggest map
Yeah, so and this map has been around for a good time period beta kind of sonar sneak this way in that's a larylac crest
but
Unlike that map you've got a pretty easy to secure natural expansion. Yeah, there's just one big ramp
But you know, it's just one ramp which uh
Actually makes it unique from some of the other maps here
But your natural is fairly secure a lot of things though and the thing is it's it takes a lot of debos to block this
You know or none as well and to be honest pull
I'm sure he'd love to like to build a wall, but then he asks himself who's gonna pay for it. Do you want to build a wall man?
Well
I could use
One debug at a time and one debug at a time it's the blue color tyranny
It's drones behind it. Pulse just needs a you know small loan of a million minerals to set up a defense
He walled to defeat this is the ramp wall at the natural like open. Yes. Yes. You shouldn't be able to breach pulse mean of course
Helians are coming out but the zerglies get on top of this bunker. He's fine. He's fine
All he's blocking the sdb's they're not gonna be able to repair us the Marines go down the Helians are going down to Jeff
He's doing great. He's he's killing the Helians. He's got two more buttons pop up a lot of damages done here
And he's taking his third base and starting his lair and he has to force the Helians rally inside his droning behind this
That's the madness like if you're still just making purelings pull could lift this up
Make four six, you know, Helians or whatever and then just kind of recover
But it's drones behind us and has been for a while
He does lift the command center at last. Be careful those scary zerglings
Yeah, they're terrifying lurking
We all he finds the sdb's that you had that's unfortunate a couple more are gonna go down now
I do like that they do tofully just return to work though like you know what
We do two things we build buildings and we mine I always like mentioning this
But I'm pretty sure in the lore s every sd has like a PhD like engineering and stuff
And then they just go out and some dudes like all right a little monster is gonna eat you alive
We didn't go to wall
If you think you have a PhD do you remember I pretty sure I read it somewhere in like wings of Liberty era
So maybe my memory is fuzzy, but I'm pretty sure all the
Exelagiously racist like character in brood war for sdb's
Yeah, but though as far as I'm sure as far as I'm aware they may have all also
T-h-t there's some jungle in town here
man
I don't judge written doctrine
I don't I don't judge
He has a theoretical degree in physics and now we have to see Pulse Backup Plan because if you look at the build that was meant to be it looks like it was going to be again that kind of
14 16-ish Marines and a gaggle of Helians, but that of course is not gonna hit any critical time
And even that build itself is a little bit weird on this map
Well, yes, the Helians can dart across and then become Helians and Medivac sir again quite quick as well
You're just actually gonna be slowed down by the expansive the map anyways
So a little bit critical of that choice. I mean he was like that's what working game one. Let's just do it again, Brett
But it's not gonna hit a meaningful timing here
man is really worried for Paul because he he basically had his legs broken here at the start of this game
He's got two command centers. Yeah, no upgrades really coming in except for stem
But he's that half his opponents supply and workers and his army is not an army that can really do
Make up a difference. It's like maybe okay. He turns the Helians into Hellbats
He pushes both Marines he has these two Medivacs
Maybe Polk makes more Polk Magic happen right now
But if he doesn't do the same amount of damage that he did in like dusk towers
No, I mean and even scowled it's a man. It's like part of the reason it worked so well last time is because he jumped on
The five initial banelings that are meant to defend this but right now
This overseer is keeping Tom and everything he knows what's coming
And he's already making those five banelings and they're gonna be made and finished before this attack gets
Yep, and it's up a total of nine banelings on the way. She's gonna follow it up with more they might have speed for pizzeris
Yeah, it's not even nine banelings. It's a vented vastly superior position to the last one and these Medivacs
He can take it to him heat from the queens he knows where he's positioning
She's gonna try what did you run that how run the Helians by so he's like no I got something I got certain things man
Fake mute is coming out too. Oh, no
Anything but the fake mutants in control the fake meters that do more damage than most people's 12 meters like
Holy crap because 12 meters it is scares you enough to do something about it's true
They're like oh three mutants. I'm never took them serious. Oh, times like what are they gonna do?
He is upgrading plus one range
With speed. Oh
Okay, well that'll happen to put by the way. He's one of the Terrence that is not actually omniscient
He's he's off doing other things humans. Yeah, he's human sometimes. That's so weird
I think it's because he goes to school if he wasn't going to school. He would have always seen that yeah
Clearly
Clearly a man that
Isn't a tough spot right now
Like I mean honestly, I'm trying to look for like positives here, but so he's already got his one one whole doesn't have his plus one yet
Um, it's bad waiting on combat shields no third command center. And he's doing yes. This isn't central protocol
You know he's doing that thing again where he's like front loading all the production and then we'll add the third CC
But especially on this map where
Applying that pressure is really really difficult. I feel like this is the pull program failing a little bit
This is like pulled hot
Applied to legacy avoidance is not working. I mean so he played the map really well with the speedling opener
Like yeah, Pulch just got completely blindsided by that run by and it did pile a lot more damage than it should out
Well, clearly it's a pull
Liberators absolutely shut down muters, right?
Depends on many he has two two muters you I mean two liberators you can spread against those
They'll help in a straight-up fight
But I think if Palt were to be attacked right now
He'd probably rather put them in anti-ground mode just to help to apart anything that moves in
Now I'd say when you get to like four liberators you can start to do something
But like liberators hit critical mass versus like any number of muters once you have like six
Because the muters will shoot their volley out while the liberators shoot and if you have like six liberators
You're actually just gonna one-shot the whole cloud of muters even if you lose all your liberators too
By the way, that's a lot more expensive for the zerg player. No third CC and
The zergling that is off screen right now just spotting that is the end of the game. I feel like
And he knows he doesn't need to do anything. Well now he just makes stuff. Yeah, just build units non-stop
Don't be greedy. He has a hive gonna finish too as well if a single drone comes out
Till the end of this game basically. I'll be very shocked
Without a third CC at this time just link bane. There's link bane it
He's gonna move in some widow mines are being brought in as well
But not getting the money hits that they need pull it needs to win the game with this bush
He choose a part the first wave of units here from solky
He has everything all his ships in this basket and solky's doing such a great job like tears of banelings
He doesn't need to win a single fight
He just needs to live and here comes the bane is dealing out the damage the force has been thinned out too much
No third behind this liberators are a non factor by the way
Pulse just having kind of a tough time controlling this
Yeah, he's having a really rough time here
And then the liberators are gonna take some shots against these muters
But the link bane remains unanswered as he surrounds the rest of Pulse army and will completely clear it up solky
Looking to take his third win here and move on there at the intel extreme masters Pulse
He's got nothing left now the parade's being shoved back again notice you see there it is Pulse GGs
32 in favor of solky a fantastic series
Uh, but I do again
Maybe it's because we have a long broadcast. I have time to not
Shoot up my emotional like just go all the way to top
But I want to be critical to pull it a little bit choosing to do it
I mean again, he was gimped a little bit at the early stage
But I feel like with that ramp and
Okay, so he hasn't done a speedling all in or real timing attack
I feel like in this entire series and for the most part he's been like defensive speedling
We'll probe a little bit but for the most part is either anticipating
Reapers or is just trying to defend
But I feel like for it to go to game five and for Pulse to do kind of a soft opening that I feel like
Without being harassed still wanted to walk across the map and be Marines and Helians. Yeah, kind of a weird choice
I think a lot of it comes down to just maybe how Pulse likes to play this matchup a lot of Korean Terrence make the focus of their games again
Zerg to be kill them before they get ultra-less. Yeah, so Pulse it worked really well in the first game
You had a much shorter rush distance. Obviously you only have that very small ramp into your main in natural
So Ling Rumbi is never gonna work
Um, I agree with you. I think I think your point that it's because of the matchup. I won't ever say to agree
But I feel like the map in the map in those positions
Shatters that played really big into it
So we can see as the bracket evolves here. We're halfway done with tonight's matches
We've got beyond facing off-sulk you guys will see that tomorrow rocks you by Paul Clariss time and wonderful
Commentators over in Taipei right now and coming up next
We have two more best of five spring you SOS will face off against MC and then snoot playing against hero
Couple a great series. I again, I'm really excited for this pvp matchup a lot of people have been bimoning a little bit
That it ends up a lot of times stalker and disruptor
But I actually think that's some of the most exciting micro in the game and everything that leads up to that is really cool as well
Faced up charge me nerfed heading into this is gonna be interesting as well
I'm curious to see how that affects pvp
But as a non-tarant as a non-pros player. I think watching stalker disruptors a bit more fun than
Seven or eight colossi just kind of attacking into each other whoever drops zealots on the other one wins
Well, so we're gonna go into that match next please and gentlemen here into extreme masters
Taipei day one will be right back after this commercial break